&gt；&gt；steve kinney：但就像他们都有一个财产一样，有什么区别，对吧？
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: But like they all have an
a property, what's the difference, right?
显然，如果我们考虑尝试删除点属性时发生的情况
Clearly, if we think about what happened
when we tried to delete points properties
从点类开始，我们考虑当我们获得不同的对象时会发生什么。
from the point class, we think about what
happens when we get different objects.
我们绝对可以测量出发生了一定程度的差异。
We can definitely measure that there is
some amount of difference that happens.
而且这真的没有任何意义，因为为什么这些中的一个会更快
And it doesn't really make any sense
because why would one of these be faster
如果它们是幻灯片就好了。&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：所以
than the other, if only they were slides.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So
原来在V8中有一个类型系统。
it turns out that there
is a type system in V8.
JavaScript中没有，但V8中有一个。
There's not in JavaScript,
but there's one in V8.
当我们看到字符串和数字时，我们对此产生了怀疑，
We had suspicions of that when we
saw the strings and the numbers,
我们的怀疑得到了证实。
our suspicions have been confirmed.
是的，数字和字符串，它会记录这些，很酷，但是
Yeah, numbers and strings,
it keeps track of those, cool, but
很明显，也有涉及物体的东西，对吧。
clearly there's something
involving objects as well, right.
我们使用的术语是态射
And the terminology we use is the morphism
那个对象，对吗？&gt；&gt；组：[笑声]
of that object, right?
&gt;&gt; Group: [LAUGH]
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：是的，每个人都回来了，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Yeah, everyone's back,
大家又来了，酷。
everyone's here again, cool.
所以我们可以说，在函数可以是单态的情况下，对吧。
And so we can say that in the case that
a function could be monomorphic, right.
还记得我们在哪里传递了一大堆只有A属性的对象，
Remember where we passed a whole bunch
of objects that only had an A property,
一个财产就是一个数字。
that A property was a number.
单形，每次都是一样的。
Monomorphic, it's the same
thing every time.
这是多态的，也就是我看到了很多东西，或者看到了一些东西。
There's polymorphic, which is I see
many things or see a few things.
有时有B，有时有C，一般都是一样的。
Sometimes there's a B on it, sometimes
there's a C, it's generally the same.
我已经看到了它的一个子集，我基本上可以在这种情况下，
I've seen it just a subset of things,
I can basically go in this case,
我要优化这里。
I'm gonna optimize here.
在另一种情况下，我将在那里进行优化，我会想出办法的。
In this other case I'm gonna
optimize there, I'll figure it out.
最后是巨型变态，
And then finally there's megamorphism,
这是一大堆不同的东西。
which is a whole bunch
of different things.
我不知道发生了什么，我不知道会发生什么。
I don't know what's happening,
I don't know what to expect.
我不会优化这种情况，对吧。
I'm not gonna optimize this situation,
right.
你可以幸运地猜一下，你想在这个频谱上处于什么位置，
You can take a lucky guess on like,
where you wanna be on this spectrum of,
我是高度优化的一种东西，主要是优化
I'm highly optimized for
one kinda thing, mostly optimized for
有几种东西没有优化，对吧。
a few kinds of things are not optimized,
right.
在这种情况下，你可以幸运地猜一猜你想在哪里。
You can take a lucky guess on
where you wanna be in that case.
这不仅适用于对象，就像我们之前看到的加号运算符。
This is not just for objects,
like the plus operator we saw before.
它的行为方式与它的行为方式不同，
Behaves way differently than it would,
当我们总是有数字的时候，有很多东西。
when we always got numbers
there's a lot of things.
一般来说，比较一致的东西是，
Generally speaking,
the more consistent stuff is,
可以进行的推测性优化越多，代码就越快。
the more speculative optimizations
can be done, the faster your code is.
所以，是的，这是总结，单形。
So yeah, here's the summary again,
monomorphic.
这就是我所知道的一切，我已经见过这种类型的物体百万次了。
This is all I know, I've seen this
type of object a million times.
我准备好了，我知道该怎么做，这是我的事情。
I'm ready, I know what to do,
this is my thing.
多态基本上是，我见过一些不同的，
Polymorphic is basically,
I've seen a few different ones,
好的，这实际上是一个切换语句。
all right,
it's effectively a switch statement.
好吧，如果是这种事，就这么做。
Okay, if it's this kinda thing, do this.
如果是另一种事情，那就做另一件事，对吧。
If it's this other kind of thing,
do the other thing, right.
你可以做其中的一些，这不是免费的，开关语句。
And you can do a few of those,
that's not free, that switch statement.
如果switch语句变得太大，
And if the switch
statement gets too large,
就像不值得了，对吧。
it's like not worth it anymore, right.
突然之间，我们都写好了代码，
All of a sudden it's like,
we've all written the code,
您可以将条件放在条件内，
where you can put a conditional inside
a conditional, inside a conditional,
内部有条件，但最终变得站不住脚，对吧。
inside a conditional, but
eventually that becomes untenable, right.
也许你们都是比我更好的程序员，但还没有做到这一点。
Maybe you're all better programmers
than me and haven't done that.
所以我们知道这并不是真正的可伸缩性。
So we know that doesn't really scale.
所以最终它放弃了，我看到了很多东西。
So eventually it gives up and
I've seen a lot of things.
我不是专业的，我只是做正常的事情，对吧。
I'm not specialized in any of them,
I'm just gonna do the normal thing, right.
我们越接近单态，我们得到的就越好。
The closer we can stay to monomorphic,
the better we get.
但这是个很好的建议，但那是不可行的，
But that's neat advice,
but that's not actionable,
这些东西是怎么工作的，对吧？
how does any of this work, right?
所以我们会稍微探索一下
So we'll kind of explore
that a little bit.
所以我们问题，
So we ask question of,
浏览器如何判断某物的类型？
how does the browser figure
out the type of something is?
我们要做的是，我们会回去做更多的实验。
And what we'll do is, we're gonna
go back to more a few experiments.
我们将看看另一个类似于特殊隐藏函数的函数
We're gonna take a look at another one of
those like special hidden functions that
基本上可以说，你们两个是一样的，对吧？
can basically say like,
are you two the same, right?
在Chrome中，每一个被称为不同的东西，
In Chrome it's called something
different in each one,
在其中一个浏览器中，形状。
in one of the browsers, the shape.
Chrome内部称它们为隐藏类或映射。
Chrome calls them hidden classes or
maps internally.
有一大堆不同的名字但是
There's a whole bunch
of different names but
大多数引擎都有一些这样的概念，对吧。
most of the engines have
some concept of this, right.
这是一种跟踪什么类型的东西是完全无类型的
It's a way of keeping track what type
something is in a completely untyped
语言。
language.